(Raj:)You know, I thought cleaning out
a dead professor's office
(Raj:)was gonna just be boring,
(Raj:)but then I found his dentures
(Raj:)and realized it's also gross.
(Howard:)Doesn't Professor Abbott's
family want any of this stuff?
(Leonard:)I don't think he had a family.
(Raj:)That's rough.
I know.
(Leonard:)You can spend your whole life
working,
(Leonard:)and at the end all that's left
are some papers in a box.
(Howard:)Makes you think.
(Howard:)Oh, well.
(Leonard:)Hey. Hey, we're supposed to
look through all this stuff
(Leonard:)before we throw it away
in case it's important.
I-I did.
It's all outdated or disproved.
(Raj:)I don't know. This old pen
kind of proves gravity.
(Raj:)When I tilt it, her bathing
suit falls right off.
WOLOWITZ:
Oh,
(Howard:)my dad used to have
a pen like that.
(Howard:)I dated it
all through sixth grade.
(Leonard:)It still feels weird
(Leonard:)just throwing away his work
like this.
(Howard:)Don't feel bad.
Someday,
(Howard:)someone will be throwing out
your work, too.
(Leonard:)That someone was Sheldon,
and the day was yesterday.